[{"answer": "No.", "docId": "130420pmt", "aSentId": 73, "question": "When all this was happening, were you in the knowledge that your parents were safe?", "qSentId": 72}, {"answer": "It was communicated to me -- what I did was, after a joint effort between my wife, myself with a cell phone, a residential phone -- so we had three phones contacting every possible number we could, to no avail, that I literally threw the phone down, ran out the back door, jumped in my vehicle, left my home here in Natick and went to my father's home in Natick to see if I could communicate better through my business and the several phones I had there.", "docId": "130420pmt", "aSentId": 91, "question": "When was the moment you were able to speak to them again and realize they were safe?", "qSentId": 90}, {"answer": "Jason, thanks very much indeed.", "docId": "130420pmt", "aSentId": 197, "question": "He said, the pain and the anger no longer a threat here in Boston -- Piers?", "qSentId": 196}, {"answer": "Chris, thanks so much indeed.", "docId": "130420pmt", "aSentId": 213, "question": "At some point, we hear that the FBI, not the hospital, the FBI will be updating his medical condition -- Piers?", "qSentId": 212}, {"answer": "It certainly has.", "docId": "130420pmt", "aSentId": 250, "question": "It's been a quite a 24 hours -- Piers?", "qSentId": 249}, {"answer": "Officials are going to study this for quite some times because police officers up there did something that's never quite been done before.", "docId": "130420pmt", "aSentId": 271, "question": "Here's CNN's Tom Foreman -- Tom?", "qSentId": 270}, {"answer": "I was -- well, you know, shocked.", "docId": "130420pmt", "aSentId": 315, "question": "And when you heard he really was nearly next door hiding in that boat belonging to your neighbor, what was your reaction?", "qSentId": 314}, {"answer": "Not at all, to be honest.", "docId": "130420pmt", "aSentId": 347, "question": "Did you get any sense when you spoke to Dzhokhar that he was getting very religious suddenly or had suddenly changed his political sentiments?", "qSentId": 346}, {"answer": "To be honest, the first time I saw the picture of the suspects on -- I saw the picture on Reddit, the picture of the suspects, you know, those were the blurry kind, at first I thought there was some resemblance there, but not enough to contact any authorities.", "docId": "130420pmt", "aSentId": 352, "question": "When you heard that it was Dzhokhar, the FBI were looking for, what was your reaction to that?", "qSentId": 351}, {"answer": "He seemed very fine.", "docId": "130420pmt", "aSentId": 364, "question": "And how did he seem to you?", "qSentId": 363}, {"answer": "No, not at all.", "docId": "130420pmt", "aSentId": 383, "question": "But he never gave you any sense of being anti-American or disenchanted with his life?", "qSentId": 382}, {"answer": "I would say he shares an American lifestyle really more than anything.", "docId": "130420pmt", "aSentId": 385, "question": "At university or anything?", "qSentId": 384}, {"answer": "Yes, yes, he does.", "docId": "130420pmt", "aSentId": 391, "question": "So you say he just sounds like a regular American?", "qSentId": 390}, {"answer": "It is a big shock.", "docId": "130420pmt", "aSentId": 397, "question": "It must be a huge shock to all of you, isn't it?", "qSentId": 396}, {"answer": "Well, I mean, you know, my suspicion and it's a suspicion is that they were.", "docId": "130420pmt", "aSentId": 430, "question": "Are we satisfied that it was just these two brothers, that the FBI seemed to be indicating that is the case, but could they have been part of a wider group?", "qSentId": 429}, {"answer": "Well, I mean, we need to know more details.", "docId": "130420pmt", "aSentId": 445, "question": "Has there been an intelligence failing here?", "qSentId": 444}, {"answer": "Yes, there's going to be a certain amount of panic in Washington.", "docId": "130420pmt", "aSentId": 460, "question": "And yet he's turned clearly, whether it's his brother's influence or what it was, if that can happen to a boy like that, is there a concern there must be the possibility of other young boys like this out there, who may also be turned?", "qSentId": 459}, {"answer": "Life imprisonment --", "docId": "130420pmt", "aSentId": 513, "question": "If they win this argument and he is found guilty in Massachusetts under their state law, what will happen to him?", "qSentId": 512}, {"answer": "-- in Massachusetts.", "docId": "130420pmt", "aSentId": 515, "question": "In Massachusetts?", "qSentId": 514}, {"answer": "It is to a federal crime, because the federal crime requires that he individually intend to coerce the government, to compel the government, to intimidate the government.", "docId": "130420pmt", "aSentId": 520, "question": "If they can prove that -- and the running theme today seems to be the older brother was a very domineering type who had become immersed in much more fundamentalist Islamic beliefs and may have coerced the younger brother, who's 19 and seems to have had no trace of any of this stuff before, into going along with this, is that any kind of defense?", "qSentId": 519}, {"answer": "I've done enough defending of unpopular people.", "docId": "130420pmt", "aSentId": 527, "question": "Would you be intrigued to defend somebody in this position?", "qSentId": 526}, {"answer": "A legal point of view, there are fascinating issues in this case.", "docId": "130420pmt", "aSentId": 530, "question": "From a legal point of view?", "qSentId": 529}, {"answer": "It does.", "docId": "130420pmt", "aSentId": 547, "question": "And this could be just the start of a whole new wave of terror?", "qSentId": 546}, {"answer": "Well, it'll either be held -- it will start in the federal court in Massachusetts.", "docId": "130420pmt", "aSentId": 554, "question": "Where would that be held?", "qSentId": 553}, {"answer": "I say, Dzhokhar, if you're alive, turn yourself in and ask for forgiveness from the victims, from the injured and from those who lived.", "docId": "130420pmt", "aSentId": 591, "question": "Why wouldn't they come together, just, you know, together as brother?", "qSentId": 590}, {"answer": "Well, it's a big question, Piers.", "docId": "130420pmt", "aSentId": 611, "question": "Or from everything that we're seeing, hearing and reading about the older brother in particular, is it more a case of him becoming immersed in Islamic fundamentalism?", "qSentId": 610}, {"answer": "Well, the statement said simply -- I believe it talks about counterterrorism issues.", "docId": "130420pmt", "aSentId": 622, "question": "Do we have any idea what they discussed?", "qSentId": 621}]